4seeking.com 2001-04-13

# 4Seeking.com Web Directory - Seek and you shall find!

|  | 

### 4SEEKING.COM Privacy Policy

4SEEKING.COM respects your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to 4SEEKING.COM will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to [contact us](mailto:webmaster@4seeking.com). 

* * *

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:**  
4SEEKING.COM does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists. 

**Browser information collected on the website:**  
4SEEKING.COM analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on website. Our website logs **are not personally identifiable** , and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site. 

**Use of cookies:**  
We don't use any cookies! 

**Privacy of our email lists:**  
We currently don't have any mailing lists. But if/when we do we'll only utilize lists that we collect ourself where Individuals must directly ask to join in. We will always include clear information on how to unsubscribe in all our mailings. We will not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on any of our future lists to anyone. In addition, email lists information will only be accessable by authorized 4SEEKING.COM staff. 

**Other websites privacy policies:**  
4SEEKING.COM incorporates search engines technologies that return results with links to other websites on the Internet. We are not responsible for any websites outside the 4SEEKING.COM domain name. Before providing your personal information to any other website, please be careful and read their privacy statements/policy. 

**Partners privacy policies:**  
4SEEKING.COM has partnerships with other leading Internet services and advertisement agencies. 4SEEKING.COM only partners with companies that have privacy policies similar to ours. Please click on any one of our main advertisement partners below to read their privacy statements (links below will open in a new window):

[**Advertising.com**](http://www.advertising.com/privacy/index.html) Ad serving prtner. (previously known as Teknosurf.com)  
[**LinkExchange.com**](http://www.bcentral.com/privacy.html) Ad serving prtner. (From Microsoft, aka bCentral.com)

---|---
